Guide to the Stanford University, Office of Development, Records SC0319
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audiovisual material, 1988-2013; Accession ARCH-2015-136
  - Celebrating an Uncommon Man and Woman: John '59, LLB '63 & Jill '63 Freidenrich DVD Running Time: 17 Minutes 2010 by the Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior Univeristy, 2010-12-10; A86; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
  - John Arrillaga An Uncommon Man 3:55, 2009-06-09; A87; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Jim Gaither An Uncommon Man, 2006; A88; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Athletics Dinner w/ Jerry Yang Tiger woods at the Cantor Arts Center audio only, 2009-11-20; A89; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Uncommon Man Video Interview with Jim Gaither Interviewer: Kyle Ozier producter/director: Randy Bean Tape #1, 2005-08-17; A90; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Uncommon Man Video Interview with Jim Gaither Interviewer: Kyle Ozier producter/director: Randy Bean Tape #2, 2005-08-17; A91; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Uncommon Man Video Interview with Jim Gaither Interviewer: Kyle Ozier producter/director: Randy Bean Tape #3, 2005-08-17; A92; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco 2005 Presidents Panel disc 1, A93; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco 2005 Presidents Panel disc 2, A94; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco 2005 Stem Cell Panel disc 1, A95; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco 2005 Stem Cell Panel disc 2, A96; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco 2005 Technology & Interdisciplinary Thinking, A97; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Stem Cell #1, 2005; A98; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Stem Cell #2, 2005; A99; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 4)
  - Thanks a billion Lunch McCaw Hall, 2006-01-05; B1; 1 videotape(s) (Mini DV) (Box 1)
  - Alumni.McCaw #48474 Donor Rel Tape 1, 2006-04-13; B2; 1 videotape(s) (Mini DV) (Box 1)
  - Ann Aud #59733 Tech Kevin K, 2006-06-29; B3; 1 videotape(s) (Mini DV) (Box 1)
  - Energy + Environment Building Reception Hi Def A, 2007-07-31; B4; 1 videotape(s) (Mini DV) (Box 1)
  - Energy + Environment Building Reception Hi Def B, 2007-07-31; B5; 1 videotape(s) (Mini DV) (Box 1)
  - Anneberg Aud Donor Relations Panel Discussion Job #59733, 2006-06-29; C1; 1 audiocassette(s) (DAT) (Box 1)
  - Bishop Auditiorum 915-945 AM, 2006-09-07; C2; 1 audiocassette(s) (DAT) (Box 1)
  - "B" Show Added for Orange Ct, D1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Jane Stanford Quote - 2 verstions #1 Source, #2 More sens./ Battle Ax #1+2, D2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - "B" Afternoon Show - Patrial Chicago + San Diego, D3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Pre-Show Music " A centry of Cardinal Rule" Approximate Time: 28 Minutes Both Sides, 1988-11; D4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Pre-Show Tape II - Marching Band "A century of Cardinal Rule" Approximate Time" 6 minutes Side A only, 1988-11; D5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Tape used is Trans. Busses in Seattle. Intro to Finale! This side: 8:06, D6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - The Stanford Challenge, Recorded at the Morgan Library NY, NY, 2006-10-17; D7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - No information, E8; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Backup DV Tape of Same - Ken, E9; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Stanford President San Francisco, 2001-01-07; E10; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Thanks a Billion Luncheon McCaw Hall 12N-130P, 2006-01-05; E11; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Volunteer Convocation for the Stanford Challenger McCaw Reel 1 VT10, 2007-04-13; E12; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - OOD Convocation McCaw 2, 2007-04-13; E13; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Living Longer Volunteer Convocation Tape #1 Fisher 2 2:30 - 3:20, 2007-04-13; E14; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Natural Capital Project Volunteer Convoction Tape #1 Fisher 1 1:30-2:20, 2007-04-13; E15; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - OOD Convocation McCaw 3, 2007-04-13; E16; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Volunteer Convocation Fac Club #3 1050-noon, 2007-04-14; E17; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Volunteer Convocation Fac Club #2 940-1040, 2007-04-14; E18; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Volunteer Convocation Fac Club #1 830-930, 2007-04-14; E19; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco master 1st session, 2005; E20; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco master 2nd session, 2005; E21; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco master 3rd session, 2005; E22; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco Cam #2 2nd session, 2005; E23; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco Cam #2 3rd session, 2005; E24; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco Cam #1 3rd session, 2005; E25; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco Cam #1 2nd session, 2005; E26; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco Cam #1 1st session, 2005; E27; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Day in San Francisco Cam #2 1st session, 2005; E28; 1 videotape(s) (dvcam) (Box 4)
  - A Stanford Saluate Justice Sandra Day O'Connor '50, LLB '52, 2006-06-23; F3; 1 videotape(s) (U-Matic) (Box 1)
  - The Uncommon Man 1994 Dinner in Honor of Mr. Peter Bing 1 hour 15 minutes, G26; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Stanford GSB 75th Anniversary 16:40, 2000-05-03; G27; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - SDI East Bay Back up, 2006-03-11; G29; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Jean Fetter aftershow, H1; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - Jean Fetter aftershow, H2; 1 film reel(s) (16mm) (Box 1)
  - #1 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-13; I1; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - #2 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-13; I2; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - #3 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-13; I3; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - #4 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-13; I4; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - #5 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-13; I5; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - #6 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-13; I6; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - #7 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-14; I7; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - #8 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-14; I8; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - #9 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-14; I9; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - #10 Roving Camera OOD Volunteer Concovation, 2007-04-14; I10; 1 videotape(s) (hdcam) (Box 1)
  - Think Again, 2001-2002; A67; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)
  - Windhover groundbreaking ceremony, 2013-06-24; 677 megabyte(s); (223 computer files)
  - Campaign College, 2006-2008
    - Campaign College, Provost Etchemendy, 2006-01-11; A1; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Panel Discussion Campaign Executive Committee Stanford Campaign College, 2006-02-14; A2; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Panel Discussion Campaign Executive Committee Stanford Campaign College, Audio Only, 2006-02-14; A3; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Stanford Campaign College, Executive Committee, 2006-02-14; A4; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Stanford Campaign College, 2006-02-14; A5; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Panel Discussion Campaign Executive Committee for Campaign College, 2006-02-14; A7; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations Alumni/McCaw, 2006-04-13; A9; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Campaign College Deans Debra Stipek + Bob Joss Audio, 2006-04-13; A10; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Stanford Campaign College, 2006-04-13; A11; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations McCaw Hall, 2006-05-22; A12; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations/Alumni/McCaw 2:30 PM CD1, 2006-05-22; A13; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations/Alumni/McCaw 2:30 PM CD2, 2006-05-22; A14; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Stanford Campaign College To: Donor Relations, 2006-05-22; A16; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations #60180 260/113, 2006-07-20; A19; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - ANN AVD #59733 Tech Kevin K., 2006-06-29; A20; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations Panel Discussion, Annenberg Aud. Job #59733, 2006-06-29; A22; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Campaign College V.2, 2006-06-29; A23; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations Campaign College, 2006-06-29; A25; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Campaign College, 2006-07-20; A28; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Campaign College PPT INTL INIT, 2006-09-20; A31; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - The Initiative on the Environment and Sustainability 2:45-4P #62288 Cubb Aud, 2006-11-15; A33; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Cubberly Auditorium Stanford University The Intiative on the Environment and Sustainability Working Solutions, 2006-11-15; A34; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Cubberly Auditorium Stanford University The Intiative on the Environment and Sustainability Working Solutions CD two, 2006-11-15; A35; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - David Lenox, Kissick Auditorium, Campaign College, 2006-12-14; A38; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Campaign College Kissick Aud David Lenox - Speaker, 2006-12-14; A40; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Kissick Aud Job #63625, 2007-01-20; A41; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations Hewlett201 #67260 239P-430P, 2007-07-23; A42; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations McCaw Hall Disc 1 of 2, 2007-03-29; A43; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Donor Relations McCaw Hall Disc 2 of 2, 2007-03-29; A44; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Alumni McCaw #63628 OOD All-Hands, 2007-02-14; A45; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Dnoor Relations McCaw Hall Campaign Arts Initiative, 2007-03-29; A46; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Office of Development OOD Campiagn College November 2007 TRT:1:15:00, 2007-11-28; A47; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Campaign College, 2008-01-10; A50; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Campaign College Clark Aud., 2007-07-25; A52; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Annual Giving Across the University Campaign College, 2007-05-24; A54; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Annual Giving Across the University Campaign College, 2007-05-24; A55; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Campaign College, 2008-04-16; A58; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Campaign College, 2008-04-16; A59; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
    - Video Master Panel Discussion Campaign Executive Committee for Stanford Campaign College, 2006-01-11; E1; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 3)
    - Donor Relations McCaw Hall #50237, 2006-02-14; E2; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 3)
    - 230-430 PM Donor Relations Alumni Center McCaw Hall ES Job #63629, 2006-02-14; E3; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 3)
    - OOD Campaign College November #1751 Table #1 of 1, 2006-02-14; E4; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 3)
    - #2209 Campaign College, 2006-02-14; E5; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 3)
    - Campaign College Stan. Off. Of Development #2210 Tape #1 of 1, 2006-02-14; E6; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 3)
    - Campaign College - April #2295 Tape #1 of 1, 2006-04-13; E7; 1 video tape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 3)
  - Ivy Conference, 1999
    - Ivy Conference Kresege Auditorium Disc 1, 2006-01-11; A60; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
    - Ivy Conference Kresege Auditorium Disc 2, 2006-02-14; A61; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
    - Ivy Conference Cubberly Auditorium, 2006-02-14; A62; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
    - Ivy Conference Disc 1 Kresege Auditorium, 2006-02-14; A63; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
    - Ivy Conference Disc 2 Kresege Auditorium, 2006-02-14; A64; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
    - Disc 1 Ivy Conference no info, 2006-02-14; A65; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)
    - Disc 2 Ivy Conference no info, 2006-04-13; A66; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 1)